[Music]
[Música]
And now we're going to see the prillo that
y ahora vamos a ver al prillo que quería
I wanted to see, the prillo with how he's doing, how he's doing
ver yo al prillo con como anda cómo anda
with the issue of the complaint that they
con el tema de la denuncia que me han
told me that he's
dicho que está
upset, they told me that he's
descompuesto me han dicho que le está
giving him the sweats, the sweaty
dando la los sudor sillos los sud
edges, [ __ ] well, it's not worth it, it's not
orillos jod pues no se le vale largo no
going to be long, this one, the sweaty edge, man, he's not going to get long,
se le vae largo a este el sud orillo tío
the sweaty edge, man, he's not going to get long, the sweaty little thing
no se le va haer largo el sudor
and it's in a bad month Yes it's true,
sillo y es en un mes malo Sí es verdad
dude, it's true it's a bad month Maybe
monce es verdad es un mes malo A lo
suddenly another month but look
mejor de repente otro mes pero mira
while we're here as we
mientras que estamos aquí como ya lo
've already put it on the main channel Well,
hemos puesto en el canal principal Pues
the truth is that something, something is growing
la verdad que algo algo está creciendo
Look, okay, something is growing, I'm telling you I mean,
Mira vale algo está creciendo ya te digo
I don't think we'll get to 20,000
O sea no creo yo que lleguemos a 20.000
or 30,000 euros but I don't know maybe I think we'll
o 30.000 eur pero no sé a lo mejor yo
get to 10, no, I don't know, I have no
creo que llegaremos a los 10 no no lo sé
[ __ ] idea, whatever is welcome
ni [__] idea lo que sea bienvenido
because it will take away all my expenses
porque me lo quitará de todos los gastos
if it is, in fact, I've already explained it
si es que de hecho yo ya lo he explicado
many times, I've been in lawsuits with these
muchas veces yo llevo en pleitos de esta
people from the gang, well  I can have
gente de la pandillita pues puedo llevar
spent 20 or 30, I can take them, it's not
gastado 20 o 30 los puedo llevar no sea
from my father, there were two pl that one we are still
de mi adre fueron dos pl que uno todavía
in them, the other is appealing the
estamos en ellos el otro recurriendo
plan we just started second the
del plan acabamos de empezar segundo la
lawsuit, the lawsuit Oli, the lawsuit against
demanda la demanda Oli la demanda al
Diego, the complaint that we filed against
Diego la de denuncia que le pusimos al
Jo Juan's friend, there is also the issue of the
amigo de Jo Juan está el tema también de
stalker, this one is very slow, very slow,
del acosador este es lentísimo lentísimo
I curse everything, how slow, eh, I have
me cago en todo qué lento eh tengo una
news about that issue every year, eh, I mean, there are
noticia de ese tema cada año eh o sea
many lawsuits, eh, There are many lawsuits,
son muchos pleitos eh Son muchos pleitos
eh, of course, you tell me many
eh claro es que ustedes me decí muchas
times, this one does not file a complaint, the other one, how did it happen, I can't go on anymore,
veces no denuncia este denuncia el otro
but well, we can't complain,
tirar Pero bueno no nos podemos quejar
no family, no at all, the one on the a, we should
no familia para nada no para nada la de
put her eh, Silvia, the one on the a, we should
la a habría que ponerla eh Silvia la de
put her
a esa habría que ponerla
eh, the one on the sixth, I ask, says Ana,
eh el de la sexta pregunto dice Ana
eh, what Ana, the one on the sixth, are you referring to the
eh el qué Ana el de la sexta te refieres
stalker, not this one I'm telling you from
al acosador no a este que te digo de
here in Seville, well, he's
aquí de Sevilla pues ese se está
waiting, he's trying to get it
esperando que está intentando que se
filed because he says that he was crazy
archive porque dice que él estaba mal de
and that he had a
la cabeza y que tenía un problema de
mental health problem or something like that, he's saying, I don't
Salud Mental o algo así está diciendo no
know, Pablo  Pablo if you ask Pablo
sé Pablo Pablo si le preguntáis a Pablo
in his live streams he will explain it
en sus directos él os lo va a explicar
better but basically he is trying to
mejor pero básicamente está intentando
claim that there should be no trial because
alegar que no haya juicio porque es que
he had a mental problem
él tenía un problema mental está
the guy is trying with all his
intentando el colega con todo su
nerve when they arrive But that happens
morro cuando llegan Pero eso le pasa
a lot to these multi-accounts that there are
mucho a las multicuentas estas que hay
on Twitter eh And the stalkers that are there
de Twitter eh Y los acosadores que hay
when you catch them later I feel like I look
cuando luego le pillas me siento miro
down crying too no oh no but
para abajo así llorand too no ay no pero
please I had a
es que por favor tenía un
problem they don't know how to salsa Well that's what I tell
problema no saben salsear Pues es lo que
you I mean many times I say don't
te digo o sea muchas veces decí no
report this one to the other man let's
denuncia este al otro al otro hombre a
see of course if I already have five or six
ver claro si tengo ya cinco o seis
open lawsuits you know Well let's see
pleitos abiertos sabes Bueno vamos a ver
the ar of Troy that the ar of Troy doesn't
al ar de Troya que al ar de troia no
have open lawsuits yet but
tiene pleitos abiertos todavía pero
well he is already thinking about having them and and it's
bueno ya está pensando en tenerlos y y
a little bit it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's
está un poquito está está chungo está
man Of course I don't
chungi está chungui hombre Claro que no
read it let's hope we don't go
lo lailo esperemos que no vamos por
please it would be a few laughs no but well
favor sería una unas risas no pero bueno
I already I already see the justice thing I
yo ya yo ya es que lo de la justicia lo
see it so random and so subjective what the
veo tan al azar y tan subjetivo lo que
same game thinks the same as you another
mismo un jueg piensa igual que tú otro
thinks  otherwise you know how those are
piensa lo contrario sabes como esos son
judges judges are people and Laticia I
jueces los jueces son personas y laticia
see her I don't know there are times when it works for me there are
la veo yo ya no sé hay veces que me da
others when it
resultado hay otros que me da
disappoints me Yes yes always always If you
decepciones Sí sí siempre siempre Si
want to see they're going to make me a trending
quieres ver me van a hacer trending
topic on social media any
topic en las redes sociales cualquier
day now I'll see myself on television on
día de estos me veo en televisión en
some channel any day any day
algún canal cualquier día cualquier día
well of the 14400 They're 200 in 4
bueno de los 14400 Van 200 en 4
days it would be 50 euros a day at 50
días sería 50 eurillos diari a 50
euros a day well it's not bad The
eurillos diarios pues no está mal La
thing is not
cosa no
10000 hbre but it's that what this one
10000 hbre pero es que a mí lo de este
does to me Thank you very much because this one
que me hace Muchas gracias porque este
doesn't even know what he's asking for And
no sabe ni para qué está pidiendo Y
also you know what he's done
además sabéis lo que ha hecho por lo
apparently eh when they've been telling him
visto eh cuando le han estado diciendo
that he could get into trouble if he
que se puede buscar un problema si le
was asking people for money for
estaba pidiendo a la gente dinero para
one thing and then used it for something else he
una cosa y luego lo empleaba en otra ha
went and wrote down all his causes in the in the
cogido y ha apuntado todas sus causas en
Go funding he wrote down
el en el Go funding ha escrito abajo
well if I don't spend it on this I'll
bueno que si no me lo gasto en esto me
spend it on the car [ __ ] it
lo gasto en el coche tomar por
Ah you know he says no no it's that the
Ah sabes es que él dice no no es que los
1400 let's see if we get them but if  you don't
1400 a ver si los conseguimos pero si no
know how much money he
sabes cuánto dinero
needs, I mean, you've put a
necesita o sea has puesto una cantidad
random amount there between
ahí al azar entre
50 we have in 28 days at the pace we're going on
50 tenemos en 28 días al ritmo que vamos
average if things don't fail at 50
de media si no falla la cosa a 50
edges on average Well in 28 days in 24
orillos de media Pues en 28 días en 24
more days I'm still in fashion trending
días más sigo siendo de moda trending
tropis trending tropis and yes
tropis trending tropis y si
And if I did this all year
Y si yo hiciera esto todo el año
wait for it 50 by 3 if I did this
espérate tú 50 por 3 si yo hiciera esto
all year I mean it's being considered that
todo el año o sea se está planteando que
the box is a modus
la caja sea un modus
vivendi if I did this all year let's
vivendi si yo hiciera esto todo el año a
see this man what happened was that he
ver este hombre lo que pasó fue que le
told his followers as if he had
dijo a los seguidores como que había
stopped
dejado
that he was on sick leave because I don't remember
de que estaba de baja por no me acuerdo
what he said something like that no and apparently
que dijo algo así no y por lo visto
according to what Pepa said it's a lie that he quit his
según contó la [__] es mentira que dejó
job because I say for what I earn
el trabajo porque digo para lo que cobro
at the ladería I sit there I start to
en la ladería me siento ahí me pongo a
rant and I do these things what's
despotricar y hago estas cosas que es lo
happening because the accounts are not
que pasa porque las cuentas no le están
coming out for him apart from that I don't know
saliendo cl aparte es que esto yo no sé
the other day in a comment he
é el otro día en un comentario que me
made to me at the end of the year he showed that he didn't
hizo a final de año demostró que no
know much about how the self-employed thing worked I
sabía mucho cómo iba lo de autónomo yo
looked up his name  in the self-employed and
he buscado su nombre en lo de autónomo y
this man does not appear in the self-employed part
este hombre no aparece en lo de autónomo
I don't know if he is doing it or what Let's
yo no sé si lo estará haciendo o qué A
see if he clarifies it Well of course H in the end
ver si lo aclara Pues claro H al final
the accounts are not adding up and now he
las cuentas no le están saliendo y ahora
invents a box with an
se inventa una caja con un presupuesto
open budget you know it's a little strange
abierto sabes es un poco raro
65 18000 Hey I put it all year and I
65 18000 Oye lo pongo todo el año y me
buy the car I do
compro el coche
n't put it all year and I buy the car
no lo pongo todo el año y me compro el
but let's see a good car no I mean
coche pero a ver un coche bueno no O sea
almost he's going to buy you a car damn
casi que te va a comprar un coche [__]
a good car no 18000
un coche bueno no 18000
bucks it's not like the baby is going to buy
pavos no es que se vaya a comprar la
a little stroller
criatura un cochecillo
for my mother my mother
para madre mía madre mía
I am that for what but there are people
Yo es que para que pero es que hay gente
who follow you eh I mean there are people there who
que sigue te eh o sea hay gente ahí que
still have people who see it I mean there's
tiene todavía gente que que lo ve o sea
always a broken one for a
es que siempre hay un roto para un
patched one there's always people there are already you
descocido ya está siempre hay gente ya
are willing to sacrifice and and you
está estáis dispuesta a sacrificar y y
give away 50 each every day
regaláis 50 illos cada cada día
ea And how do you see it 50
ea Y usted de qué cómo lo veis 50
pavillo a
pavillo al
day how do you see it 50 euros a
día cómo lo veis ustedes 50 eurillos al
day
día
that comes to not even 1 euro a month  each
eso viene ha ser ni 1 eur al mes cada
one
una
eh damn Well that's why you have
eh [__] Pues para eso tienes abiertos
the
los
members open Let's see let's do the math 30
miembros A ver vamos a hacer cuenta 30
by 50
por 50
15 10000 a month isn't bad either it would be
15 10000 al mes tampoco está mal sería
a box each month one box each month one
una caja cada mes una caja cada mes una
box each
caja cada
table I don't see it I see it I see it
mesa no veo lo veo lo veo claro
totally clear when I finish with this one I'll put
totalmente cuando acabe con esta pongo
another one of 14 14 or 15000 n your 2027 is going to
otra de 14 14 o 15000 n tú 2027 va a
do like this gu my god the
hacer Hacienda así gu madre mía viene el
troll is coming in through the door and
trollo está entrando por la puerta y
a large backpack is coming it will be for
viene una mochila grande será para
us we have to put the video of
nosotros hay que poner aquí el vídeo de
Paquita sala and the trending topy here mother of
Paquita sala y el trending topy madre de
God yanch Okay then there I am I'm
Dios yanch Bueno pues ya está lo estoy
seeing it I don't have the level of Olivera
viendo yo no tengo el nivel del Olivera
or the level of the flight when it comes to
ni el nivel del vuelo a la hora de
collecting you go to a box but I can
recaudar vas a una caja pero sí puedo
put the permanent box and the people who
poner la caja permanente y la gente que
are donating but if it's that you already
vaya donando pero si es que eso ya lo
have it or so that doesn't make sense of
tiene o sea que eso no tiene sentido
course look at what you're doing eh I
claro fijaros lo que está haciendo eh o
mean
sea
eh You don't have the level of the flight the
eh Tú no tienes el nivel del vuelo el
level of Javi that people donate to you
nivel de Javi de que la gente te done
but of course if How are people going to donate to you
pero claro si Cómo te va a donar la
if you are  asking him with a little
gente si estás pidiéndole con un poco
shame you don't know why we're going
vergüenza no sabes para qué vamos vamos
to see
a ver
eh you don't have to put up a
eh tú no tienes que poner una caja
permanent box to collect but if you already
permanente para cobrar pero si eso ya lo
have that, I mean you have your members you don't
tienes o sea tú tienes tus miembros no
have the members The Super chat your
tienes los miembros Los Super chat tu
visit is clear that is the
visita claro es esa es la caja
permanent box now then
permanente ahora luego
eh Now then something comes up not
eh Ahora luego que te surge una cosa no
unexpected or or or you have a move not
improvisto o o o tienes una movida no
like the one I just mentioned the
como la que acabo yo de comentar el
main channel and and people want to
canal principal y y la gente te quiere
help you well Okay perfect [ __ ]
ayudar pues bueno Vale perfecto de [__]
great completely legal but a
madre completamente lícito pero una caja
permanent box does not even know what he is
permanente no sabe ni lo que está
asking for
pidiendo
straight from October 1, 2023 he already
directo del 1 de octubre del 2023 él ya
said that he paid
dijo que pagaba
autonomous that he had the first years a
autónomo que tenía los primeros años una
reduced fee they send me
cuota reducida me mandan
Ah well look according to him according to him yes
Ah pues mira según él según él sí pag
self-employed pay well then
autónomo pues entonces así no le salen
the accounts do not add up of
las cuentas
course m I could do it perfectly one
claro m podía hacerlo perfectamente un
year I buy the second-hand car it would
añito me compro el coche de segunda mano
no longer be used it would be a car already
ya no sería de ocasión sería un coche ya
good with its year But hey launch
de bueno con su año Pero oye estrenar
2027 with a second-hand car Well it
2027 con coche de segunda mano Pues
's not bad either no And for the next one
tampoco está mal no Y para el siguiente
I ask for a tent for the entrance of the apartment of the
me pido para la entrada del piso una
calón he
tienda de campaña del de calón eso
says quickly but  troll post the
rápido dice pero trollo fija el
link on Monday to see what they tell me
enlace el lunes a ver lo que me dicen
because on Monday I'm going to
porque el lunes yo voy a a
investigate on Monday it feels like this one is
investigar el lunes se siente pero este
going to investigate and I'm going to the police station to have them
va a investigar y voy la comisaría a que
look for that complaint filed in my
me busquen esa denuncia puesta a mi
name using my
nombre utilizando mi
name to advertise and
nombre para hacer publicidad y
generate and generate apart from generating
generar y generar aparte de generar
audio because they are using it for
audio porque lo están utilizando para
that on different channels well I'm going to
eso en diferentes canales pocillo voy a
see if the complaint is true
ver si la si la denuncia es cierta
because today I checked again with
porque hoy he vuelto a comprobar con
another
otra
person and the same defects
persona y los mismos defectos de forma
let's say So I had the one I
digámoslo Así que tenía con la que
compared previously, I have it again
comparé anteriormente vuelve a tenerla
with this one So nothing fits me and
con esta Entonces no me cuadra nada y yo
on Monday I'm going to find out if I have it I'm
el lunes me voy a enterar si la tengo
going to try to get a copy
voy a intentar hacerme de de una copia
because I suppose I have the right to be
pues Supongo que tengo derecho a que me
given one and if it's not posted then I will make it
den una y si no está puesta pues haré
public that it's a lie like
público que eso es una mentira como el
Mr. Hello Charo Martín very
día del señor Hola Charo Martín muy
good evening
buenas noches
and the one who says she has
y a la que te Según dicen te ha
sued you is a lie, she has not sued you, it
demandado es mentira no te ha demandado
is a complaint
es una denuncia
raffi it is a complaint
raffi es una denuncia
and if she hasn't filed it they are going to have
y si no la ha puesto van a tener
problems they are going to have problems she for
problemas van a tener problemas ella
sure and the channels that have echoed
fijo y los canales que se han hecho eco
and shown that little paper possibly
y mostrado ese papelito posiblemente
also well with 200 she will have  that to
también pues con 200 va a tener que
distribute there I don't know how you're going to pay it to
repartir ahí no sé cómo vas a pagarlo a
everyone eh whatever but besides what the hell are
todos eh sea pero aparte qué [__] es lo
you going to report today is Monday it wasn't
que vas a denunciar hoy es lunes no fue
Nuri Look here the protagonist Nuri
Nuri Mira está aquí la protagonista Nuri
eh Let's see he says that if you don't
eh A ver él dice que si tú no le
report him he can report
denuncias é él te puede de denunciar a
you why I mean exactly
ti por qué O sea exactamente el Por
why and the channels that we've talked
qué y a los canales que hemos hablado
about the subject too but exactly
del tema también pero exactamente el Por
why I mean I don't really understand what
qué O sea no entiendo muy bien cuál
the crime would be Well of course
sería el delito cometido Pues claro
taking into account that this man went to the
teniendo en cuenta que este hombre fue a
police station this morning to
la comisaría echa la mañan yaa para
report us for laughing at him because
denunciar noos por reírnos de él porque
he himself published an audio imagine
él mismo publicó un audio imagínate
now he doesn't even know what he wants to
ahora no no sabe ni lo que quiere
report with the 200 I mean this one
denunciar con los 200 o sea este se
shows up there with the 200 and some euros
presenta ahí con los 200 y pico de euros
on a lawyer And he's capable of saying to her take
en un abogado Y es capaz decirle toma
how much can I report with
Cuánto puedo denunciar con
this I already say that for her own good for the good
esto yo ya digo que por su bien por el
of all I hope it's set up now
bien de todo Espero que esté puesta ya
if the player arrives no I'll take care
si llega el jugado no ya me encargaré yo
of answering what I have to answer
de responder lo que tenga que responder
But like that That one is screwed eh this one it
Pero como esa Esa está cago eh esta se
occurred to her to write a little paper
le haya ocurrido hacer un papelito ella
by hand And  pass it through the channels and
a mano Y pasarlo por los canales y
deceive him they are going to have problems they are going to
engañarlo van a tener problema van a
have quite a few problems carcasi but
tener bastantes problemas carcasi pero
in the POA they have a certain little [ __ ] that
en la poa tienen cert cagadita que está
Enrique
la nrique
says complainant find side like I don't
pone denunciante encuentre lado como no
know what And there is no
sé qué Y no hay ningún
stamp you see that there is no
sello ves que no hay ningún
stamp There is no stamp and the stamp is
sello No hay sello y el sello está
surrounded by a line this is a
rodeado por una línea esto es una
kind of smudge that is
especie de manchur rón que hay
there a kind of smudge And if you
ahí una especie de manchur rón Y si os
look at the thumbnail the
fijáis en el de la miniatura el la
thumbnail does
miniatura sí lo
have it it will be because of the light issue or
tiene será por el tema de la luz o
because it is not the same part don't see
porque no es la misma parte no a ver
side Oh look Yes it is true it is true look
lado Ah mira Sí es verdad es verdad mira
side if you look at the thumbnail it is
lado si fijáis en el de la miniatura es
true look at the one here in this one you can't
verdad mira en el de la aquí en este no
see the stamp Look it is white and here
se ve el sello Mira está blanco y aquí
what is the answer in the
cuál es la respuesta en el de la
thumbnail It is true the thumbnail does
miniatura Es verdad la miniatura sí lo
have it it is true you understand And that is why that is what
tiene es verdad entendéis Y eso por qué
calls my attention it says
que es lo que a mí me llama la atención
police in the little circle
pone policía en el circulito
of this detail has the
de este detalle se ha daado cuenta la
person that I with whom I that you
persona que yo con la que yo que se te
missed a detail says on a on the page
pasado un detalle dice en un en el folio
where they took the thumbnail that
donde han sacado la miniatura ese sello
police stamp  it's not but what sense would it
de policía no está no pero qué sentido
make if there were two
tendría que hubiera dos papeles
different papers, I mean if it
diferentes o sea en el caso de que no
wasn't there none of them would be no I mean they've made
estuviera no estaría ninguno no O sea
two it's not there I hope they
que han hecho dos no está Espero que
're taking note the bollards and the
estén tomando nota los bolardos y la
Perry Mason the Perry a police station And if
Perry Mason la Perry una comisaría Y si
this complaint hasn't been filed at the
esta denuncia no está puesta en
police station prepare the body both the
comisaría preparar el cuerpo los dos los
three or I'm involved in this trust
tres o los estoy metido en esto fíate
this man with 50 and some stick going to
este hombre con 50 y pico palo yendo a
the police station to ask this
la comisaría a preguntar esta
nonsense you can
tontería tú te lo
imagine because I'm going to point out all the
imaginas porque voy a señalar todos los
channels where this
canales donde se ha mostrado esta esta
complaint has been shown And what And what is he going to say to the
denuncia Y qué Y qué va a decir a los
channels that have shown the complaint let's
canales que han mostrado la denuncia a
see It's that here he's telling me to
ver Es que aquí me está diciendo que
look
mire
Salomé okay here they're putting another
Salomé vale aquí vuelven a poner otra
photo where you can see more clearly
foto donde se ve ya más clarísimamente
the issue of the seal
el tema del sello
okay But then what's
vale Pero entonces que es lo que
going on What's the
pasa Cuál es la
deal What's the discussion then
movida Cuál es la discusión entonces
Sara reyar Sara reyar doesn't solve it eh
Sara reyar Sara reyar no lo soluciona eh
I think it's not the same stamp
yo creo que no es el mismo sello
ea obviously s ryar Thank goodness they
ea evidentemente s ryar Menos mal que
always face it you see that the signature is There
siempre lo acara veis que está la firma
had to be the people's signature
Tenía que estar la firma de la gente
on top of it it's in a  side without
puesta encima está en un lateral sin
catching the text which is not
pillar el texto que es una cosa que no
very normal
es muy normal
but then if I enlarge the little stamp
pero luego si amplío el sellito de de
here it says
marra aquí
poli the Li has been eaten it's as if it had
poli el Li se lo han comido es como si
fallen letter from the stamp yes yes no that no that
se lo hubieran caído letr del sello sí
tinín it's not because the
sí no eso no eso tinín no es porque la
administration doesn't have ink for the
administración no tenga tinta para el
stamp the stamp could be irregular because
sello sello puede ser irregular porque
the ink is already drier or it hasn't been
ya tiene la tinta más seca o no haya
wetted the pad but here there are missing
Mojado El tampón pero aquí faltan
letters it could also be that this stamp
letra también puede ser que esta sello
has been scanned from somewhere
la hayan cogido escaneado de algún sitio
and they had to erase this and that's why it's
y hayan tenido que borrarte esto y por
missing letters if you don't
eso faltan letras que si no te pones a
look at it Ah they made photocopies So
mirarlo Ah que se hicieron fotocopi O
not all of them are the same paper
sea que no todos son el mismo papel que
some are photocopies and others are not Oh
algunos son fotocopias y otros no Ah con
calmly okay so everything that is
tranquilidad vale o sea que todo lo que
scratched everything that is scratched is
rayado que todo lo que está rayado es
because it is true that there are two
porque sí que es verdad que hay dos
photographs so there are photographs on
fotografías o sea que hay fotografías a
really different papers So yes he is
papeles diferentes de verdad O sea que s
partly right no in that there are
tiene razón el en parte no en que hay
different papers I am missing the
papeles diferentes me falta lo de
Melilla part that is missing that yes but that is that we clear up
melilla le falta eso eso sí pero que eso
the doubt Luna I go to
salimos de la duda el Luna me acerco a
the command to that one and  and I ask the one on
la comandancia al ese y y pregunto el de
the
la
right no because let's see the one on the
derecha no porque a ver el de la
left has But it has lost ink it's
izquierda ha Pero ha perdido tinta es
as if it had lost a lot of
como si si hubiese perdido un montón de
ink it has a lot of it's missing a
tinta tiene un montón de le falta un
lot of details that this one has if
montón de detalles que tiene este si
you look at it later, I mean, one is a
luego te fijas o sea uno es una
photocopy and the other isn't the composition yes the
fotocopia y otro no la composición sí
upper invoice everything matches
que factura superior coincide todo con
the letters the position and
las letras la posición y
everything, it could be scanned but
todoo puede puede estar escaneada pero
damn what a worse scan no Yoli Panda
[__] queé escane más malo no Yoli Panda
the one from chalom has the crease in the paper
la de chalom tiene el pliegue del papel
yes from having had it folded the other one doesn't
sí de haberla tenido doblada el otro no
have any of those no Folded the one
tiene ningún de esos ningún Doblado el
that is the photocopy doesn't have any
que es la fotocopia no tiene ningún
Folded that reaches its place it's going to have it that
Doblado que llega a su sitio va a tener
also responds to other things
ella que responde también a otras cosas
and letters too Antonio has lost yes he
y letras también Antonio ha perdido sí
has lost letters extinct circle has
ha perdido letras extinta círculo ha
lost everything from being the scanner is
perdido todo de ser el escanner es una
crap the
[__] el escanner que han usar es una
scanner that they have used is poop well I'll leave you for a minute I'm going to is scared sillo no no they are different stamps Darío if it even has the same position the stamp that is a photocopy that has eaten part of the stamp let's see if everything is in its place
sello a ver si está todo en su sitio
is scared no ant  the first one they
está asustao no ant la primera la
prepared quickly to put it on the
prepararon rápido para sacarlo en el
live channel and the second one
canal el directo y la segunda la
they made with more time but they are not the
hicieron con más tiempo pero no son
same I have no idea if it's good or
iguales no tengo ni idea si es buena o
not it's good it has to be in the database you
no es buena tiene que estar en la base
know what I mean if it's in
entendé lo que quiero decir si está en
the database it's up if it's not
la base de datos está puesta si no está
in the database it's not
en la base de datos no está
up we're going to laugh for a
puesta nos vamos a reír un
while on Tuesday because I'll
rato el martes porque el lunes
rest on Monday on Tuesday I promise you
descansaré el martes os prometo
exclusive without wanting to but there is a
exclusiva sin querer pero hay una
reasonable suspicion
sospecha razonable
man my first suspicion for not
hombre yo mi primera sospecha por no
getting the lyrics it's not normal it
pill las letras no es normal
c a
se c un
[Music]
[Música]
cigarette yeah he's not calm eh He's not
cigarrillo sí no está tranquilillo eh No
calm
está tranquilo
eh he stays mouth humming are
eh se queda bucal canturrear son
symptoms of nervousness let's see
síntomas de nerviosismo a ver
gu is nervous
gu está nervioso
eh he's overwhelmed eh pass by it's that man
eh está agobiados eh pas por es que tío
with these
que con estas
things is that put you close man
cosa es que ponerte asecto tío
well thank you thank you thank you thank you
bien gracias gracias gracias gracias
this one comes in handy too men
esta me viene de [__] madre tamb mén
this one I'm going to
esta la vo a
save this one I'm going to save thanks
guardar está la voy a guardar gracias
chalom thank you another another one that is
chalom gracias otra otra otra que está
always pending Thanks for clearing up my
siempre al pendiente Gracias por sacarme
doubt it seems like it's good eh
de la duda parece que es buena eh
family seems like it's good now
familia parece que es buena ahora le
I'll show him the photo now I'll show the  photo
enseño la foto ahora enseño la foto
Look it seems like it's good, eh see Let's
Mira parece que es buena eh
see,
veis A ver
save it,
guardalo
oh what happened over
ay qué paso por
here There it is, that's the other stamp that we could
aquí Ahí está esa es la otra sello que
n't see well Let's see, you can see it well, no Antonio
no veíamos bien Vamos a ver ya lo está
Sing sing, you can see it
Antonio Canta canta ya lo estás viendo
well, no
bien no
Antonio, the database doesn't come over
Antonio la base de datos no vente para
here so I can see one and another,
aquí que yo vea una y otra
okay, okay
bueno bueno
[Music]
[Música]